# MICHELLE LIM AK LAUNCESTON DAVE

+6016-2423323 | michelleakdave@gmail.com | Semenyih, Malaysia | https://www.linkedin.com/in/michelledave/

## **SUMMARY**

A keen final year student and result-oriented individual with an information systems engineering background from UiTM Shah Alam. Well experienced in developing front-end part of web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript & jQuery for nine months and equipped with problem-solving, adaptability and analytical skills as well as teamwork and communication skills.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

EJEN2U Putrajaya, MY

Frontend Developer - Contract

Mar 2022 – May 2022

- Worked closely with senior UI/UX developers and designers to brainstorm and develop product features to boost agent management within the current market.
- Identify and fix features that contain bugs on the user interface side of the SaaS.

EJEN2U Puchong, MY

Internship Sept 2021- Feb 2022

- Learned and practiced web platform development and best practice from experienced developers within the company. (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Git, Project Management)
- Identified and debugged 70% of the bugs for the front-end part of the production system to enhance the user experience and system's overall performance.
- Developed a "Forgot Password" feature for the system which simplifies account recovery and strengthened the system's security.

## **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

# UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA

Shah Alam, MY

Bachelor of Information Systems (Hons.) Information Systems Engineering

2023 - Present

Cumulative GPA: 3.53/4.0

Relevant Coursework: System Requirement & Analysis; Software Improvement; System Design & Implementation; Database Engineering; System Testing & Evolution; Enterprise Architecture Framework

# UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA

Sungai Petani, MY

Diploma of Computer Science

2019 - 2022

Cumulative GPA: 3.89/4.0; Vice Chancellor Award Graduate.

Relevant Coursework: Algorithm Design & Development; Algorithms & Problem Solving; Object-Oriented Programming; Database Management; Data Structure; Web & Mobile Application Development

#### **PROJECTS**

# **Counseling Management System**

Aug 2024

- Designed and developed the user interface part of the counseling management system which enables administrators to manage patients' data, counselors' data as well as manage appointments.
- Language/framework utilized: Java EE, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

# Fit Gym Membership Registration System - Web & Mobile Application

July 2021

- Designed and developed alongside team members a gym membership registration system for both web and mobile application to ease the gym's membership registration.
- System features include managing gym member's personal data, making membership payment, view payment status, confirm payment, make appointments, view appointments, update appointments, view appointments and generate report.
- Language/framework utilized: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, MySQL, MIT App Inventor, JSON

May 2020

- Designed and developed a simple online banking system which enables users to enter bank account pin number and make a transaction.
- Applied one-time password feature before allowing user to successfully make their transactions.
- Language/framework utilized: Java

# PERSONAL SKILLS

#### Languages:

- Professional working proficiency in English and Malay.
- Elementary proficiency in Mandarin.
- Native proficiency in Bidayuh.

#### **Soft Skills:**

Problem-solving, debugging, adaptability, teamwork, communication and analytical thinking.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### Languages:

• Experienced in HTML, CSS, Java, SQL, JavaScript, Python, PHP, C++, C, jQuery and Java EE.

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Dean's List Award (Bachelor of Information Systems (Hons.) Information Systems Engineering)
  Semester 3 to semester 4.
- Vice Chancellor's Award (Diploma of Computer Science, 2022)
- Dean's List Award (Diploma of Computer Science, 2019 2022)

## PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATE

## Certified Professional for Requirements Engineering – Foundation Level (CPRE-FL)

Oct 2024

Malaysian Software Testing Board

Skills acquired: Requirements Engineering

## REFERENCES

# Nurafiqah Najaa Firaberi

+6019-6225324 | <u>afiqahnajaa.95@gmail.com</u>

Internship Supervisor (Industrial)

Ejen2u International Sdn. Bhd.

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nurafigahnajaa/